Adam Schefter is joining us right now
from uh here in New York City.
Obviously, we've got to check in with
you, Adam, before this draft begins.
What can you tell us is going on?
>> The other team looking to go up in the
first round is the New York Jets. They'd
like to get into the top 15 picks,
presumably to get one of the draft's
top-rated cornerbacks, but the Jets have
made some calls to move up, which is a
rarity these days with so many teams
looking to move back. And obviously,
it's always fun when the Jets or the
Giants are on the clock here at a draft,
and it's even more fun when one of them
is surprisingly on the clock with a a
big trade. Mike Mayock, your thoughts?
Uh I'm kind of already on the record
here. I don't think they will because I
believe John Fox
Wait a minute. What happened? The Jet
fans have just exploded because a trade
did just in fact take place. The Jets
have now been put on the clock,
which means fasten your seat belts,
everybody.
Oh, boy. A first trade. That guy in the
Belcher jersey was asleep 2 minutes ago.
Now he's up.
>> Now, do we want a corner here, or do we
want Brady Quinn? We took Kellen Clemens
a year ago in the second round to be the
quarterback of the future.
>> Look at that guy right there. We got a
pick coming up.
>> I hope these guys don't start booing the
pick. Hey, what is he saying, Rich? What
is he saying? He's saying, "Sit down, so
I can be on TV."
Adam Schefter, what can you tell us
what's going on?
>> [laughter]
>> Well, the Jets have been trying to trade
up all morning, trying to get into the
top 15 picks. They finally worked it out
where they could get up to Carolina's
spot. The Jets now have their choice of
cornerbacks. They can take whichever
cornerback they believe is the top-rated
corner in this draft. Could be Darrelle
Revis from Pittsburgh, could be Leon
Hall from Michigan, but the Jets have an
opportunity to get the cornerback that
they've been trying to get all morning.
There you go. So, the Jets, apparently,
are going to get themselves a a corner.
It's uh Darrelle Revis out of
Pittsburgh, Leon Hall out of Michigan.
We'll see which one uh the Jets covet.
Who do you think it's going to be? You
know, all year long Leon Hall was
perceived to be the number one corner in
the country. When Darrelle Revis, the
junior from Pitt, came out, the only
question was long speed. What would he
run? He ran in the 437 range. When you
put tape on a both of them, I like Revis
better for what the New York Jets do.
>> Up there they are. They woke that up, I
guess. They did. They did. They woke up.
They got Martin jerseys. They got
Pennington jerseys. Maybe they'll have
Revis jerseys next year. Or Hall. Who
knows? Here we go. Here we go. Straight
from the trade desk.
Let me see if I can give you the details
on this trade.
>> [laughter]
>> Carolina has traded its first-round
pick, which is number 14 overall,
their sixth-round pick, which is number
199 overall,
for the Jets' first pick,
25 overall, their second pick,
59 overall, and their fifth pick, which
is number 164 overall.
Oh, here they the selection.
All right, that's all we're getting
right now. That's all we're getting
right now is the
the contents of the trade, which has set
the Gang Green faithful
>> [cheering]
>> a little bit of buzz.
>> They don't like the contents.
>> It's too expensive.
They wanted it
>> It's New York. It's New York. It can't
be too expensive, Rich. The Jet fans are
on pins and needles as the Jets, I
guess, are spending the next 5 minutes
deciding who to take. It's a Mike
Tannenbaum decision, an Eric Mangini
decision. What's going on in the Jets'
draft room right now, Steve?
>> Well, they moved up for a reason. I
They're not trying to trade this pick.
They're trying to acquire a certain
player, and I think they've got their
guy in mind. I don't know what's taking
them so long to turn it in because I'm
sure they know. The one thing for sure
is uh there's a lot of enthusiasm in
here to be curbed as the Jets are right
now about to give their pick, which we
assume will be uh either Revis out of
Pittsburgh or Leon Hall out of the
University of Michigan. Let's see what
Roger Goodell has to say. The
commissioner is coming out from the
wings, getting the last word from Greg
Aiello of the league, and here he is to
the delight of the Jet fans.
Sit back and enjoy. The Jets are about
to make a pick. It's got to be Revis.
With the 14th pick in the 2007 NFL
Draft,
the New York Jets select
Darrelle Revis, cornerback, Pittsburgh.
I'd say that's mixed.
Would you call that mixed?
>> I think in New York, mixed is good.
Yeah, that's not bad for here.
>> in my opinion, this is the best corner
in the draft.